-----Chinese-----
软件授权使用协议
（请务必在下载之前阅读此协议）

下载安装本公司提供的相关软件后，被视为同意本协议的所用内容。

本软件属免费软件。允许自由用于个人使用和公司业务。
但无论免费还是收费，不得将本软件放在可供第三方下载的网站上。
本软件的著作权归属于英富美盛科技（北京）有限公司。
使用者不得通过任何技术手段更改其中的内容，
也不可将其作为任何软件的一部分来使用或销售。
本公司对于在使用本软件时可能发生的、使用者的
直接或间接的或偶然的损失不负任何赔偿责任。


此软件可以做到：
当你需要将旧的程序代码（例如：VC++ 6.0的代码）转换成VS2008可用的Unicode的代码时候，
可以选用此软件。
1.所选文件夹之下的所有文件（包括子文件夹下的）的字符码都被转换围Unicode。
2.自动获取相关文件的当前的字符码种类。
3.通过预览窗口，确认文件，并视情况修改所选文件的当前的字符码种类。

执行环境：
Windows 10以上 + .NET 4.0以上

安装及其使用方法：
1.首先要确认是否安装了.NET 4.0或更高的版本。如果没有，可以到微软的网站下载安装。
2.把此中的所有文件复制到你的PC的硬盘中。
3.执行ReCharSet.exe

-----Japanese----
ソフトウェア使用許諾契約
（使用する前に必ずお読みください）

　お客様は、本ソフトウェアをインストールして使用することにより、
　本契約の内容に同意したものとみなします。

　本ソフトウェアはフリーソフトウェアです。お客様は、個人的使用・業務上の使用ともに、
　本ソフトウェアを自由に使用することができます。ただし、有償無償を問わず、
　本ソフトウェアを第三者に配布する（第三者がアクセスすることのできるような状態で
　ネットワーク上に本ソフトウェアを置くことも含む）ことはできません。
　本ソフトウェアの著作権は英富美盛科技（北京）有限公司に帰属します。
　お客様がリバースエンジニアリング、逆コンパイル、逆アセンブルなど解析すること、
　改変すること、他のソフトウェアに組み込むことはできません。
　本ソフトウェアを使用したことにより被ったいかなる直接的、
　間接的または偶発的損害も保証、賠償いたしません。


本ソフトの目的は過去に作られたソースコードを全て一括してUnicodeに変換する。
例えばVC++6.0で作ったソースはたいていS-JISであるため、
VS2008で扱いづらくのなるので、変換したほうがよいだろう。
このソフトの機能は以下の通りとなっている
１．サブフォルダも含めて選択されたフォルダ以下にある全てのテキストファイルをUnicodeに変換する。
２．関係テキストファイルの文字コードタイプを自動的に検知する。
３．選択したテキストファイルをプレビュー表示して、内容確認できる。
　　状況に応じて現行文字コードタイプを変更できる。

実行環境
Windows 10以上 + .NET 4.0以上

セットアップと実行
１．まず.NET4.0がインストールされていることを確認してください。
　　なければ、マイクロソフトのホームページからインストールしてください。
２．ここにある全てのファイルをハードディスクの適切なところにコピーしてください。
３．ReCharSet.exeを実行してください。


-----English-----
What this applictation can do for you.
Most of old C++ source codes are written by local character code, such as ASCII code,GB code or S-JIS code.
You may want to convert those source code to UNICODE.
This software can do following job for you.
1.Change character code to Unicode for all the file under select directory.
2.Find out the original character coding type from each source code file automaticlly.
3.Preview the text contents of selected file. and you can set the character coding type for the select a file.

Supported OS:
Windows 10 or higher + .NET 4.0(or Higher)

 
How to install it an use it.
1.First of all ,check your windows system supprot .net framework 4.0 or higher.
  If not, install it first. your can find the install program from Microsoft WEB site.
2.Copy all these file to proporly holder.
3.Run ReCharSet.exe.
